<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SimpleAgar</title><link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/</link><description>Recent content on SimpleAgar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>SimpleAgar</copyright><atom:link href="https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3-2-1 Agar Agar Cups</title><link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120421agarcups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120421agarcups/</guid><description>Materials Agar Agar Powder Corn Flakes, Potato Flakes Corn Syrup Food Coloring Quart/Pint Jar w/ Lid Scale that weighs in grams Stovetop, top burner grill Pressure Cooker How to? Weigh out 3 grams of potato flakes into quart jar. Weigh out 2 grams of Agar Agar Powder into same quart jar. Weigh out 1 gram of Corn Syrup into same court jar. Add 1/2 cup of water to the jar.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started - Start Here</title><link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120121gettingstarted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120121gettingstarted/</guid><description>Where do I begin? So you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to start growing mushrooms. So, what&amp;rsquo;s next? So, where do you begin? You attempted to use the search function, but there is so much information. You have no idea what questions to ask, let alone what strategy to use. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of contradicting information out there.
The Breakdown Mushroom cultivation requires 2 basic things: You need to grow mycelium on a substrate, then get that mycelium to produce mushrooms.</description></item><item><title>NoPrep Perfect Grain Jars:50:50 Oats/Millet Version</title><link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120221noprepperfectgrain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120221noprepperfectgrain/</guid><description>Difficulty I personally made 40quart jars, with two 23q pc&amp;rsquo;s including the pressure cooker time in about 3 hours. Materials Whole Oats Whole Millet/Bird Seed Quart or Pint Jars Water Food grade scale Pressure Cooker Optional - Clean funnel How to? Oats - Quart Jars 1.) 235grams of oats //
2.) 165grams of water
Millet/Birdseed - Quart Jars 1.) 250grams of millet/birdseed
2.) 160grams of water</description></item><item><title>SGFC using PF/BRF Cakes</title><link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120321sgfcusingpfbrfcakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/posts/120321sgfcusingpfbrfcakes/</guid><description>BRF Cakes, cakes, and PF Cakes are all different names for the same thing. They are made of brown rice flour(BRF), vermiculite, and water. Once these cakes are made and sterilized, you add spores, the spores germinate, and mycelium starts growing. Once the mycelium is finished growing and consolidating, these cakes are birthed, dunk and rolled, and placed in a SGFC for fruiting.
SGFC stands for Shotgun Fruiting Chamber and is called this because of its appearance; it has a bunch of holes in it.</description></item></channel></rss>