<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SimpleAgar</title>
    <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SimpleAgar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>SimpleAgar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 19:49:57 -0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started?</title>
      <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/start/gettingstarted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 19:49:57 -0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/start/gettingstarted/</guid>
      <description>Where do I begin?  So you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to start growing mushrooms. So, what&amp;rsquo;s next? So, where do you begin? You attempted to use the search function, but there is so much information. You have no idea what questions to ask, let alone what strategy to use. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of contradicting information out there.
 The Breakdown 1.) We are going to need some genetics Order spore prints, spore swab of your choice online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NoPrep Perfect Grain Jars:50:50 Oats/Millet Version - by Uncle Al</title>
      <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/jars/noprepperfectgrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 19:52:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/jars/noprepperfectgrain/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty Beginner
Materials  Whole Oats Whole Millet/Bird Seed Quart or Pint Jars Water Food grade scale Pressure Cooker Optional - Clean funnel  How to? Oats - Quart Jars 1.) 235grams of oats
2.) 165grams of water
Millet/Birdseed - Quart Jars 1.) 250grams of millet/birdseed
2.) 160grams of water
Oats &amp;amp; Millet - Quart Jars 1.) 130grams of oats
2.) 130grams of millet/birdseed
3.) 170grams-180g of water
 Choose what method you are going to use Per method, weigh out the amount of substrate Per method, weigh out the amount of water Put the lid on the jar if you dont have a hole with papertape in the lid, put the metal lid on upside down and tighten Place all of the jars you made up into a Pressure Cooker Add water to PC after all the jars are in, I usually go 1/2 the way up the jars that are standing in the bottom of PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SGFC using PF/BRF Cakes</title>
      <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/brfcakes/sgfcusingpfbrfcakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/brfcakes/sgfcusingpfbrfcakes/</guid>
      <description>BRF Cakes, cakes, and PF Cakes are all different names for the same thing. They are made of brown rice flour(BRF), vermiculite, and water. Once these cakes are made and sterilized, you add spores, the spores germinate, and mycelium starts growing. Once the mycelium is finished growing and consolidating, these cakes are birthed, dunk and rolled, and placed in a SGFC for fruiting.
SGFC stands for Shotgun Fruiting Chamber and is called this because of its appearance; it has a bunch of holes in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-2-1 Easy Agar Cups - by Philly Golden Teacher</title>
      <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/agar/agarcups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/teks/agar/agarcups/</guid>
      <description>Materials  Agar Agar Powder Corn Flakes, Potato Flakes Corn Syrup Food Coloring Quart/Pint Jar w/ Lid Scale that weighs in grams Stovetop, top burner grill Pressure Cooker  How to?  Weigh out 3 grams of potato flakes into quart jar. Weigh out 2 grams of Agar Agar Powder into same quart jar. Weigh out 1 gram of Corn Syrup into same court jar. Add 1/2 cup of water to the jar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/about/contactus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://currrie.github.io/agarblog/about/contactus/</guid>
      <description>Contact us: email: support@simpleagar.org discord: www.discord.gg/sCXCjwWc facebook: www.facebook.com/groups/simpleagar </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
